I understand correctly that Russia
я правильно понимаю что ро Россия войска
revealed troops And in return they didn’t get anything
выявила А взамен ничего не получила
Let me finish Let me finish, I’ll be
Дайте мне договорить Давайте
interested then I’ll listen to you, let’s Hello Hello, I’m
интересно потом вас послушаю давайте
from the
давайте Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из
city of Khmelnitsky You’re from Sevastopol Cool
города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
And
Севастополь Прикольно А в Севастополь
where did you
откуда
get to Sevastopol born in Sevastopol cool
попали родился в Севастополь прикольно
That is, you were in the fourteenth year
То есть вам вы в четырнадцатом году были
adult Yes of course Oh super That
совершеннолетний Да конечно О супер То
is, you saw all these events There is
есть вы видели все эти события Там
Girkin and so on Yes super yes I understand well
гиркина и так дальше Да супер да понял
look I understand that you can’t
ну смотрите Я понимаю что вам нельзя
talk a lot because the
много очень разговаривать да потому что
FSB will be able to talk in bottles Yes well you frankly
ФСБ сможет на бутыли Да ну вы откровенно
won’t be able to talk because there is a
не сможете говорить потому что там
Crimean mix  it works, yes But the question is
Крымский смеш работает да А вот вопрос
how do you talk, you say yes, well,
какта Поговорите вы говорите да да ну
if you can speak, say yes,
если если сможете говорить говорите да
answer my question as a
отвечайте у меня вот такой вопрос как
resident of Sevastopol, yes, a year ago, for
жителю Севастополя да э год назад ещё
example, yes, Ukrainian missile strikes on
например да украинские ракетные удары по
Sevastopol were considered some kind of
севастополю это считалось какой-то
fantasy, yes, but now not now  already
фантастикой да А сейчас не сейчас уже
there, Nurm flew to the headquarters of
там нурм прилетел в штаб
the Sevastopol Black Sea
севастопольского этого Черноморского
Fleet, then a boat flew in to Feodosia, in
флота тут Феодосию прилетел кораблик
short, today something
короче сегодня ещё в Севастополь что-то
else arrived in Sevastopol,
ж прилетело да у
how about you, so Putin is allowing strikes on
вас как так что Путин допускает удары по
Sevastopol Well, the fact is that you understand
севастополю Ну фак в том что понимаете
this, firstly, this is, firstly, a conflict
это во-первых это во-первых конфликт как
how can they be prevented Tell me Well, I don’t
как их можно не допустить Скажите Ну не
know, there’s
знаю там уничтожить
one country to destroy everyone, not a single country, not a single
всех одна страна ни одна страна ни одна
country in the world, in short, that’s who is
страна мира короче это само кого От
not immune from this, remember how it was in
этого не застраховано помните как было в
Israel, in short, they had a scorched iron
Израиле короче палёный там железный
dome there, they said that we have the best
купол у них они говорили что у нас лучше
in the world  there it is he himself and what does not break through
в мире там это само он и что пробивает
? Well, for example, why doesn’t Putin
аж не Ну например почему Путин Не
hit the British on the table and say
стукнет британцам по столу и не скажет
that? Stop giving these missiles to the Ukrainians
так Перестаньте украинцам давать эти
Storm Shadam because they are
ракеты Шторм Шадам потому что они по
hitting in the Crimea Well, I
Крыму лупят
honestly don’t know this. Damn,
Ну вот это вот я не знаю честно Вот блин
just me too I thought  I was thinking like,
просто я тоже Я думал Я думал как типа
uh, Putin will tell the British to
что ээ Путин скажет британцам
the Americans, just in short, give your
американцам только короче дадите ваше
weapons, we’ll hit you with nuclear weapons and
оружие мы ядер кой бахнем по вам и всё
they’ll all get scared, we were really
они все испугаются мы реально этого
afraid of this, the British, and the British in general, this is the
боялись британцев а британцев вообще это
most important thing to scare them, in principle, you don’t need to hit
самое их в принципе попугать не надо по
them, you just need to hit him like that
ним надо просто как его как ударить
In short, they live there on the islands,
Короче они же там на островах живут да
yes, and the island would go to the bottom, well, well, in short, they are
да и остров бы пошёл бы по дно ну
stupidly stubborn,
типа ну они короче они они тупо упоротые
these British, they are stupidly
вот эти британцы они тупо короче
stubborn, they give us everything, like they were the
упоротые они дают нам всё типа они
first to give us, in short, damn all sorts of
первые дали нам короче блин всякие там
cool things at the beginning of the invasion
прикольные штуки в начале вторжения
now damn the Storm Shadow missile was not given the first one.
сейчас блин ракета Шторм Shadow первая
Well, it flew across Sevastopol in leather across the
не дали Это ж вот по севастополю коже
Black Sea Fleet; they are silent; they
прилетала по черноморскому флоту молчат
are silent. So that’s how it should be in principle. Damn, how can that
молчат Значит так надо в принципе Блин а
be? Putin doesn’t give a damn about the fact
как так на то есть Путину насрать на то
that sailors are dying. I don’t know. In principle,
что гибнут морячки Я не знаю В принципе
if I were if  If I were in
если бы я был бы если бы я был бы с на
his place, I would honestly
его месте то я бы честно говоря
focus on Kiev. I would
сосредоточил бы внимание на Киев Я бы
start robbing right away. Kiev is
начал шать бы сразу Киев он находится
close, very strong.
близко сильно сильно
Kiev, so it turns out that a bunch of people
Киев так получается куча куча людей
are killing Bakhmut Avdeevka there. Yes, they
убивает там бахмут авдеевку Да Киев же
won’t take Kiev. Well, like, this is already for everyone  it’s clear,
не возьмут Ну типа это уже всем понятно
like yes, that is, Why won’t anyone take Kiev? Well, they
типа да то есть Почему не возьмут Киев
ran away from Kiev and are
кто Ну убежали от Киева и там где-то
fighting somewhere, in short, in the Donbass, wait,
бьются короче на Донбассе подождите
wait, Yes, I’m waiting, they ran away, first of all, they
подождите Да жду убежали во-первых
ran away. Let’s sort it out with you,
убежали Давайте с вами так разберёмся
look at the agreements that we are
смотрите договорённости что мы как
weakening military activity. These are the
ослабляя военную активность Вот какие
agreements the agreements were  in
договорённости договорённости были в
Istanbul What kind of agreements What were
Стамбуле Какие договорённости О чём
agreed upon in Istanbul where where can you see
договорили в Стамбуле где где можно
these agreements where can you
посмотреть эти договорённости где можно
read the text of the agreement then what
почитать текст договорённости потом что
then what did you photograph them Look,
потом что вы их фотографировали Смотрите
look, there are Minsk agreements we
смотрите есть минские договорённости мы
can on the website quietly I'll tell you the other one you
можем на сайте ти хо я вам другому вы
watched in short this is the interview of Orakha
смотрели короче это само интервью ораха
and Machu  no no I didn’t look I don’t understand I
и Мачу не не я не смотрел я не понимаю я
I trust the documents I trust the document
я доверяю документам я доверяю документа
What was agreed upon what was agreed upon in
О чём договорились о чём договорились в
Istanbul if there were any
Стамбуле если были какие-то
agreements What was agreed upon in
договорённости О чём договорились
the first place
вопервых
How it was I as I understand it to myself That
Как там было я как я себе понимаю То
is, as I see from our media how  I
есть как я смотрю из наших СМИ как я
see from your media It’s not just that That
смотрю из ваших СМИ Это не просто То
is, Arakhamia gave an interview Well, I Pony
есть арахамия давал интервью Ну я Поня
gave What did you agree on that you were
давал О чём договорились что вы
taking troops away from Kiev And what was there in return, which
забираете войска от Киева А что взамен
means that in short, according to our
там было значит что короче по нашим
points, according to our points, it really means
пунктам по нашим пунктам реально значит
non-aligned
внеблоковый
status, non-aligned status, then this was also
статус нековый статус потом это ещё было
Well, that is, I understood, in short, a lot of everything,
Ну то есть я понял короче куча всего
look, I understand correctly that
смотрите я я правильно понимаю что
Russia has identified troops And in return
Россия войска выявила А взамен ничего не
received nothing to agree on Let’s be
получила договорить Давайте
interested in you, the ambassador Come on, that is, the
интересно вас послу Давай Давайте то
first was bloc status,
есть первое было блоковый статус вот
then there was a special status for Donetsk, separately for these
потом особый статус донецко отдельно эти
regions of the Donetsk and Lugansk regions
областям Донецкой и Луганской области
That’s really there  there was something else there,
Вот реально там ещё что-то там ещё
something else was shorter, here’s the bloc, and
что-то было короче вот блоковый вот а и
you recognize Crimea, you recognize Crimea, that
Крым признаёте вы признаёте Крым это
meant that, but the fact is that
было вот значит что но факт в том что
when Arakhamia said, as they tell us here according to
когда арахамия сказал как нам здесь
our news according to our
говорят по нашим новостям по нашим
analysts, that
аналитикам то
is, remove the troops from-  near Kiev, that is,
есть Уберите войска из-под Киева то есть
Kiev in the semi-ring, really remove
Киев ла полу кольце реально уберите у
our deputies from running away, really, that
нас депутаты по разбегались реально то
is, who where we can’t gather a council
есть кто где мы не можем собрать совет
so that these agreements are ours,
чтобы чтобы вот эти вот соглашения наши
that is, like that you will withdraw the troops and our
то есть типа что вы отведёт войска и нас
deputies will come to Kiev to vote
депутаты приедут в Киев проголосовать
? No, well then  there is to assemble the supreme one,
Да нет ну то есть собрать верховную раз
yes yes, that is, that is correct, arahamia
да да то есть то есть правильно арахамия
told Putin that Putin should withdraw the troops
сказал Путину чтоб Путин отвёл войска
because the deputies cannot come to Kiev.
потому что депутаты не могут в Киев
Putin said oraha, well, like
приехать Путину сказал ораха ну типа
yours there, some incomprehensible dude
вашим там каким-то непонятным чувака
Dinsky there, yes, here’s a
динскому там да
howl from you Ukrainian Children have come to
вот вой от ваы украински Дета прили в
Kiev  could have
Киев могли
voted to reduce military activity
проголосовать снизить военную активность
That's how it was, that is, the troops, the
Вот так это было то есть войска войска
troops withdrew, the
отвели войска отвели
troops withdrew, but the troops
ноп войска отвели чтоб что не для чего
withdrew so that there was nothing for why they withdrew the troops so that
для чего отвели войска для того чтобы
Ukrainian deputies would come to Kiev I
украинские депутаты приехали в Киев Я же
told you yes, the Supreme Council did not work
вам сказал да Верховный Совет не работал
because the
потому
martial law badge  I understand that
что военное положение бляха Поня я вот
you explained this to me for the first time in so many
это вы вы мне вы мне первый за столько
years, because everyone says that the
лет объяснили потому что все говорят что
troops simply withdrew. And now I
это просто отвели войска А теперь я
understand that this is so that
понял то есть это для того чтобы
deputies from the regions can come to
депутаты могли из регионов приехать в
Kiev to gather in the Verkhovna Rada. Well, it’s
Киев собраться в Верховной Раде Ну это
like ours  it’s like ours all Well,
так как наши вот это как наши всё Ну
now my puzzle has come together Yes,
теперь у меня пазл слал сложился Да так
look good, the deputies have arrived [ __ ],
смотрите хорошо депутаты приехали [__]
I can’t help but laugh, wait, come on, so the
я не могу не ржать подожди давай так
deputies, the deputies, the deputies came to
депутаты депутаты депутаты приехали в
Kiev and decided not to vote, what is
Киев так и решили не голосовать что
Russia doing next, what is it not not
Россия дальше делает что она не не то
that they didn’t decide not  the fact that they didn’t decide to
что не решили не то что не решили
vote, but look at what
голосовать а том что смотрите что
Arakhamia says. Then all sorts of
говорит арахамия Потом приехали всякие
advisers came, all sorts of advisers. From America. From
советники всякие советники С Америки С
Britain, they told the deputies that
Британии сказали депутатам голос мы с
Russia and I won’t sign anything, so I
Россией подписывать ничего не будем вот
understood everything, yes, well, what did Russia
и всё понял да хорошо то Россия что
do, what did Russia do then,
сделала Россия что сделала тогда Россия
she returned the troops  Well, if Russia
она вернула войска Ну если бы Россия
then, well, if you don’t want to sign, returned the
тогда ну а не хотите подписывать вернула
troops back and captured
назад войска и захватила
Kiev, no then it was
Киев нет тогда уже Это было нереально
unrealistic then it was already
как нереально тогда уже это было
unrealistic. Why Well, because these
нереально А почему Ну потому что это
were the first what’s-his-name days
были вот Вот первые как его как там дни
there there for what a month and a half  how
там там сколько там полтора месяца как
they stood near Kiev in principle Yeah,
под Киевом стояли в принципе
damn it doesn’t hang up such an interesting
Угу блин не зависает такой интересный
Sevastopol resident just doesn’t
севастополец просто не
hang up
зависает
So in our tion treasury Nova bike,
Итак в наший ций скарбнички Нова байка
you’ll be aware of
вы зрозумити
Eva so that the deputy can go to
Ева чтоб депутат могли пожа в
Kiev, I really didn’t bother streaming so that they’re not
Киев я реально не змиг стримати щоб не
clamped Tod put plus who really stayed
зажаты Тод поставьте плюс кто реально
on whom haha ​​Tsei  versions Yes, in
кого на хаха пробыл Цей версии Да
short, they are withdrawing the troops, well, Arakhamia
короче они отводят войска ну арахамия
says Yes, withdraw the troops. Well, so that
говорит Да Отведите войска Ну чтобы
our deputies come to Kiev
депутаты у нас приехали в Киев потому
because they can’t have a deputy. And like, the
что они не могут чтобы депутата А типа
deputies came to Kiev. It turns
депутаты в Киев Приехали тут ещё
out that American advisers
оказывается советники американские
arrived together with the deputies, they say
приехали вместе с депутатами говорят
no, I can’t, just
не я не можу ну просто
Jacques, I really have this version of chulti Yes, they
Жак реально я такой версии чул ти Да они
took it so that the deputies would
отвели для того чтоб депутаты
come write to my Telegram directly at the same
приехали пись на мий Telegram прямо
time, the axis of wines, but
зараз ось вин а
for now it’s even more and more
пок це дуже и дуже
polite
важливо